Guide to the Julia Driver Collection of Women in Photography
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Card Photographs and Other Photographic Materials, 1845-1940; Series II; 5.83
  - Photographic Materials
    - Jones, D. W., Mrs. (born circa 1828), 1867-1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 290)
      Active in Greenville, South Carolina, 1867-1870
      Also known as Mrs. W. B. Jones
    - Jones, Matilda, Mrs. (born 1860), circa 1895; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 8, Folder 291)
      Active in Del Norte, Colorado, circa 1895-1920
      Also known as Mrs. C. H. Jones or Mrs. Charles H. Jones
    - Jonn, Lina, (1861-1896), circa 1880-1896; (3 cartes-de-visite and 1 cabinet photograph) (Box 8, Folder 292)
      Active in Lund, Sweden, circa 1880-1896
      Also known as Carolina Johnsson or Mrs. Gudbrand Tandberg
    - Jonn, Maria, circa 1900; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 293)
    - Jube, Mary Ann Sidell, Mrs. (1820-1881), circa 1860-1865; (4 cartes-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 294)
      Active in New York City, circa 1856-1865
    - Jurvelius, Helene, circa 1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 295)
      Active in Finland, circa 1880
    - Kail, Jennie, Mrs. (born circa 1857), circa 1885; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 8, Folder 296)
      Active in East Liverpool, Ohio, circa 1885
    - Karlström, Theres, circa 1900; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 297)
      Active in Sollefteå, Sweden, circa 1900
    - Kay, Ellen, Mrs. (born circa 1830), circa 1881; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 298)
      Active in Bolton, England, circa 1881
      Also known as Mrs. Thomas Kay
    - Kellett, Sarah E., Mrs. (born circa 1841), 1880-1887; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 299)
      Active in La Porte City, Iowa, 1880-1887
      Also known as Mrs. T. A. Kellett or Mrs. Thomas A. Kellett
    - Kemp, S. E., Mrs., circa 1890; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 8, Folder 300)
      Active in South Pittsburg, Tennessee, circa 1890
    - Kendall, Marie Hartig, Mrs. (1854-1943), circa 1910; (2 photographic postcards) (Box 8, Folder 301)
      Active in Norfolk, Connecticut, as well as Brookline, Massachusetts, circa 1880-1910
      Also known as Mrs. J. C. Kendall or Mrs. John C. Kendall
    - Kenyon, E. S., Mrs., circa 1860; (8 cartes-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 302)
      Active in Somerville, New Jersey, circa 1860
      Includes a view of a church.
    - Kindberg, Maria, circa 1895; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 303)
      Active in Gnesta, Sweden, circa 1895
    - Klopot, Clara Keithline, Mrs. (1871-1968), circa 1896; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 8, Folder 304)
      Active in Chicago, Illinois, as well as North Judson, Indiana, 1896-circa 1930
      Also known as Mrs. Sigmund Klopot
    - Knorring, Caroline von, (1841-1925), 1867; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 305)
      Active in Stockholms Län, Sweden, 1864-1871
      Composite photograph that depicts twenty-three teachers in Skara, Sweden
    - Knox, Cornelia, Mrs. (1864-1930), circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph and 1 card photograph) (Box 8, Folder 306)
      Active in Lakeview, Oregon, 1900-1925
      Also known as Mrs. Clara A. Watson or Mrs. John N. Watson
      Includes a portrait of Edna Faye Heryford Young (1883-1968)
    - Koch Laurent, Madame, circa 1885; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 307)
      Active in Geneva, Switzerland, circa 1885
    - Krone, Ella, Mrs. (born 1852), circa 1880-1889; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 308)
      Active in Decatur, Illinois, circa 1880-1889
      Also known as Mrs. Charles Krone
    - Kruse, Anna, circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 8, Folder 309)
    - Kuylenstjerna, Hilda, circa 1890; (5 cartes-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 310)
      Active in Borås, Sweden, 1886-1902
    - Lacey, Julia, Mrs., circa 1890; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 9, Folder 311)
      Active in Morristown, New Jersey, circa 1880-1890
      Also known as Mrs. E. G. Lacey or Mrs. Edward G. Lacey
    - Läckgren, Ester, circa 1890; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 312)
      Active in Nösund and Laholm, Sweden, circa 1890
      Portrait of two women posed standing with a St. Bernard dog
    - Lagerstam, Anna Elin, (1877-1966), circa 1915; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 313)
      Active in Nyköping, Sweden, 1905-1942
      Also known as Ella Lagerstam
    - Lajoie, Victorine C., Madame (born circa 1855), circa 1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 9, Folder 314)
      Active in Montreal, Quebec, circa 1880-1900
      Also known as Madame V. Lajoie
    - Lancaster, Elizabeth, Miss (born 1881), circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 9, Folder 315)
      Active in Rome, Georgia, circa 1900
    - Langdon, Clara, Mrs., circa 1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 316)
      Active in St. Louis, Missouri, circa 1870
    - Larson, Betty, circa 1910; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 317)
      Active in Växjö and Kristianstad, Sweden, 1895-1919
      Portrait of a girl holding a cat
    - Larsson, Maria, circa 1899-1900; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 318)
      Active in Sandviken, Sweden, circa 1899-1900
    - Lasinsky, Laura, (1844-1919), circa 1885; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 319)
      Active in Düsseldorf, Germany, circa 1885
    - Lautrup, Augusta, circa 1895; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 320)
      Active in Korsør, Denmark, circa 1895
    - Lavis, Rebecca Finlason, Mrs. (born circa 1827), circa 1860-1870; (8 cartes-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 321)
      Active in London and Eastbourne, England, circa 1860-1880
      Also known as Mrs. George Lavis
      Includes discrete portraits of sisters Ellen Griffin and Kate Griffin, circa 1870
    - Law, Pearl, Miss (born circa 1869), circa 1890; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 9, Folder 322)
      Active in Hot Springs, Arkansas, circa 1890
    - Lawrence, Emma J., Mrs. (born 1840), circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 9, Folder 323)
      Active in Union City, Michigan, circa 1900
      Also known as Mrs. J. S. A. Lawrence or Mrs. John S. A. Lawrence
    - Lawton, Mary Elizabeth "Lizzie" Shumway, Mrs. (born 1836), circa 1860-1870; (14 cartes-de-visite and 1 tintype) (Box 9, Folder 324)
      Active in Willimantic, Connecticut, 1865-1881
      Also known as Mrs. A. J. Lawton or Mrs. Andrew J. Lawton
    - Leavitt, A., Mrs., circa 1870-1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 325)
      Active in Oakland, California, circa 1870-1880
    - Lebour, Mademoiselle, circa 1860; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 326)
      Active in Paris, France, circa 1852-circa 1865
    - Lefrén, Louise, circa 1890; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 327)
      Active in Stockholm, Sweden, circa 1880-1900
    - Leigh, M. E., Mrs., 1876-1879; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 328)
      Active in Ionia, Michigan, 1876-1879
      Includes a portrait of Alice York (born circa 1855) from Easton, Michigan
    - Leland, M. A., Mrs., circa 1870; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 329)
      Active in New York City, circa 1870
    - Lesher, Mary A. Holler, Mrs. (born 1834), circa 1862-1864; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 330)
      Active in Shippensburg and Carlisle, Pennsylvania, circa 1862-1864
      Also known as Mrs. J. C. Lesher or Mrs. John C. Lesher
      Includes a portrait of William Wenk (born circa 1825) of Menallen, Pennsylvania. He reportedly died in Libby Prison at Richmond, Virginia, during the American Civil War
    - Levi, Clara H., Mrs. (born circa 1838), circa 1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 331)
      Active in Abilene, Kansas, circa 1880
      Also known as Mrs. C. H. Levi, Mrs. Clarissa H. Levi, or Mrs. Henry Levi
    - Lewis, Alice, Mrs. (born 1855), 1896-1910; (5 cabinet photographs) (Box 9, Folder 332)
      Active in Celina, Nevada, Ohio, 1896-1910
      Also known as Lewis and Wife or Mrs. Ford Lewis
    - Lewis, J. B., Mrs., 1884 November; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 9, Folder 333)
      Active in Greenwich, Connecticut, as well as New York City, circa 1880-1893
    - Lewis, Sarah J., Mrs. (born 1852), circa 1899; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 9, Folder 334)
      Active in Clark and Huron, South Dakota, 1887-1899
      Also known as Mrs. A. T. Lewis or Mrs. Abram T. Lewis
      Portrait of Carl E. Behrens (born 1885)
    - Libby, Minnie F., Miss (1863-1947), circa 1886-circa 1905; (1 carte-de-visite and 4 cabinet photographs) (Box 9, Folder 335)
      Active in Harrison and Norway, Maine, circa 1886-circa 1940
      Also known as Miss Libby
      Includes a childhood portrait of Dr. George Harold Shedd (1882-1964), circa 1886, and a group portrait that includes Nettie Ira Morrill Burgess (born 1884), Ethel Florence Morrill Gibbs (born 1881), and Georgia Irish Bell (born 1881), circa 1905
    - Liljegren, Fanny, circa 1900; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 336)
      Active in Vännäs, Sweden, circa 1900
    - Liljeqvist, Regina Maria, circa 1890; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 337)
      Active in Oulu, Finland, circa 1890
      Also known as Ina Liljeqvist
    - Lindman, Elvira, circa 1890-1900; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 338)
      Active in Skillingaryd, Sweden, circa 1890-1900
    - Lindquist, Anny, Miss, circa 1889-1900; (5 cabinet photographs) (Box 9, Folder 339)
      Active in Chicago, Illinois, circa 1889-1900
      Also known as Lindquist and Berglund or North Shore Studio
      She had a studio partnership with Hannah Berglund.
    - Lindstedt, Ebba, circa 1900-1917; (41 cartes-de-visite and 5 cabinet photographs) (Box 9, Folder 340)
      Active in Örnsköldsvik, Sweden, circa 1900-1917
    - Linsén, Maria Natalia, circa 1900; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 9, Folder 341)
      Active in Borgå, Finland, circa 1900
      Portrait of two children posed sitting with a dog
    - Lipczyński, Nanny, Frau, circa 1898-1899; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 10, Folder 342)
      Active in Dresden, Germany, circa 1898-1899
      Also known as Adolf Hoffmann Atelier
    - Ljungkvist, Arvida, 1912; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 343)
      Active in Västervik, Sweden, circa 1912
    - Lockwood, Alvira, Miss (1845-1923), circa 1870; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 344)
      Active in Ottawa, Canada, circa 1870
    - Lockwood, Eunice N., Mrs. (born circa 1841), 1879-1883; (4 cartes-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 345)
      Active in Ripon, Wisconsin, 1868-1889
      Also known as Mrs. E. N. Lockwood, Mrs. W. N. Lockwood, or Mrs. William N. Lockwood
    - Lockwood, M. L., Miss, 1876-1886; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 10, Folder 346)
      Active in Almonte, Canada, as well as Lisbon, North Dakota, 1876-1886
      Also known as Miss M. R. Lockwood
    - Long, Cora W., Mrs., circa 1892-1894; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 10, Folder 347)
      Active in Azusa and Los Angeles, California, circa 1892-1894
      Also known as Mrs. C. B. Long
    - Long, Louisa C., Mrs. (born 1859), circa 1900-circa 1920; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 10, Folder 348)
      Active in Edgerton, Ohio, circa 1900-circa 1920
      Includes a group portrait of Gaylord A. Richardson (born 1898), Leah L. Richardson (born 1900), and Nellie A. Richardson (born 1902), July 1904
    - Lord, C. A., Mrs., circa 1870; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 349)
      May be Miss Amelia Carman (born circa 1849) after marriage, who listed the same working address in Corry, Pennsylvania
      Active in Corry, Pennsylvania, circa 1870
    - Lord, Emma F., Miss, circa 1871; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 350)
      Active in Sparta, Wisconsin, circa 1871
      Also known as Mrs. Lorenzo F. Cofrin
    - Lowe, Minnie, Mrs. (born 1864), circa 1900-1920; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 10, Folder 351)
      Active in Westcliffe and Silver Cliff, Colorado, circa 1900-1920
      Also known as Mrs. M. Lowe, Mrs. Amelia Lowe, or Mrs. Cassius Lowe
    - Lowengrim, Louisa, Miss (1861-1950), circa 1900; (3 cabinet photographs) (Box 10, Folder 352)
      Active in Boonville, Missouri, circa 1900-1910
      Also known as Miss Alouisa Lowengrim
    - Lucore, Emma Hollister, Mrs. (born circa 1848), circa 1890; (4 cabinet photographs) (Box 10, Folder 353)
      Active in Fort Worth, Texas, 1888-1893
      Also known as Mrs. James Bassett Lucore or Lucore & Ward
      Lucore was in a partnership with Gurney E. Ward, 1888-1891
      Includes a portrait of Ellen Jane Ewing (died 1915)
    - Ludovisi, Señora, circa 1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 354)
      Active in Valencia, Spain, circa 1870-1880
    - Lummis, Hellen M. B., Mrs. (born circa 1838), circa 1871-1880; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 355)
      Active in Watkins, New York, circa 1871-1880
      Also known as Mrs. E. F. Lomis, Mrs. E. F. Lummis, Mrs. Edward F. Lummis, or E. F. Lummis & Lady
    - Lund, Kirstine, (1852-1948), circa 1890; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 356)
      Active in Hjørring, Denmark, 1882-1910
    - Lundborg, Hanna, 1904; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 357)
      Active in Piteå and Umeå, Sweden, circa 1879-1904
    - Lundmark, Mia, circa 1898; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 358)
      Active in Haparanda, Sweden, circa 1898
      Portrait of a boy posed sitting with a dog
    - Lundwall, Julia, circa 1885; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 359)
      Active in Lund, Sweden, circa 1885
    - Lyon, Mary Ann, Mrs. (born 1847), 1891-1898; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 10, Folder 360)
      Active in Woodbine, Iowa, 1891-1898
      Also known as Mrs. D. D. Lyon or Mrs. Daniel D. Lyon
    - Madden & Robbinson, Misses, circa 1864-1866; (4 cartes-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 361)
      Active in Cleveland, Ohio, circa 1864-1866
    - Madden, Mary Hadley, Mrs. (born circa 1825), 1858-1866; (4 cartes-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 362)
      Active in Shelby, Ohio, 1858-1866
      Also known as Mrs. M. Madden or Mrs. James Madden
    - Malmberg, Libbe, circa 1890; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 363)
      Active in Stockholm, Sweden, circa 1890
    - Marsh, A. L., Mrs., circa 1885; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 10, Folder 364)
      Active in Clay Center, Nebraska, circa 1885
    - Martin, Mrs., circa 1869; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 365)
      Active in Austin, Texas, circa 1869
    - Maxwell, M. M., Miss, circa 1860-1869; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 366)
      Active in Pine Run, Michigan, circa 1860-1869
    - Mayall, E., Mrs. (born circa 1838), circa 1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 367)
      Active in Clapton Park (London), England, circa 1870
    - Maynard, Hannah Hatherly, Mrs. (1834-1918), 1875-1912; (4 cartes-de-visite, 8 cabinet photographs, and 1 card photograph) (Box 10, Folder 368)
      Active in Victoria, Canada, 1862-1912
      Also known as Mrs. Richard Maynard
      Includes a portrait of a sailor in uniform, as well as a view of a boat with fourteen men holding oars
    - McCafferty, Matilda "Tillie" B., Miss (born 1847), circa 1870; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 369)
      Active in Columbus, Wisconsin, circa 1870
      Also known as Mrs. T. B. McCafferty or Mrs. T. B. French
    - McIntire, J. J., Mrs., circa 1890; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 10, Folder 370)
      Active in Spencer, South Dakota, circa 1890
      Portrait of a woman knitting a blanket and accompanied by a girl.
    - McKenzie, Jeanette, Miss, 1871-1875; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 371)
      Active in North Lansing, Michigan, 1871-1875
      Also known as Miss J. McKenzie
    - McKinney, Goldie, Miss (born 1874), circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 10, Folder 372)
      Active in Russiaville, Indiana, circa 1900
    - McMullin, Laura E., Mrs. (born 1859), circa 1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 10, Folder 373)
      Active in Marion, Kansas, circa 1890-1900
      Also known as Mrs. J. F. McMullin or Mrs. Josiah F. McMullin
    - McPhee, Catherine, Mrs. (born circa 1852), 1874-1885; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 374)
      Active in Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1874-1885
      Also known as Mrs. Catherine McFee, Mrs. James McPhee, or City Hall Gallery
    - Medlar, Elizabeth A. Curtis, Mrs. (born 1845), circa 1880; (3 cabinet photographs) (Box 10, Folder 375)
      Active in Rockford, Illinois, circa 1880
      Also known as Mrs. James Medlar
    - Mellish, Mrs., circa 1875; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 376)
      Active in London, England, circa 1875
    - Merwin, F. & M., Misses, 1866-1868; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 377)
      Partnership between sisters Frances A. Merwin (born circa 1838) and Marion A. Merwin (born circa 1840)
      Active in Newton Falls, Ohio, 1866-1868
    - Meurisse, Madame, circa 1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 378)
      Active in Béziers, France, circa 1880
    - Middleton, Sarah Ann Trindall, Mrs. (born circa 1843), circa 1885; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 10, Folder 379)
      Active in Pembroke Dock, Wales, circa 1871-1891
      Also known as Mrs. William Trindall or Mrs. George Middleton
      Portrait of a man posed standing with a dog
    - Miller, Miss, circa 1895; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 380)
      Active in Ballyshannon, Ireland, circa 1895
    - Miller, Mrs., circa 1860-1867; (4 cartes-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 381)
      Active in St. Catharines, Canada, circa 1860-1867
      Includes views of the Decew Falls and the Novelty Works foundry, as well as a portrait of Helen Kilman with an infant
    - Misick, Ida Amanda Dailey, Mrs. (1855-1928), circa 1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 10, Folder 382)
      Active in Bancroft, Michigan, 1891-1897
      Also known as Mrs. W. A. Misick or Mrs. Warren A. Misick
    - Monson, Mary Hannah Pochin, Mrs. (circa 1831-1873), circa 1865-1870; (5 cartes-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 383)
      Active in Northampton, England, circa 1855-1873
      Also known as Mrs. Charles Monson
    - Monty, Julie, circa 1895-1900; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 384)
      Active in Copenhagen, Denmark, circa 1895-1900
    - Moore, Dora, Mrs. (born 1860), circa 1895; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 10, Folder 385)
      Active in Piper City, Illinois, circa 1895
      Also known as Mrs. G. L. Moore or Mrs. George L. Moore
    - Moore, Matilda, Mrs. (born circa 1832), 1860-1869; (23 cartes-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 386)
      Active in New York City, 1860-1869
      Includes two portraits of Gilman Dudley
    - Morrill, Sarah E., Mrs., 1862-1864; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 387)
      Active in Coldwater, Michigan, 1862-1864
      Also known as Mrs. S. E. Morrill
      Includes portraits of Eldad Barber (born circa 1802) of Florence, Ohio, and his wife, Hannah Osborn Barber (born circa 1804)
    - Morris, Harriet, Mrs. (born circa 1838), circa 1875; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 388)
      Active in Battersea, England, circa 1875
      Also known as Mrs. H. Morris or Mrs. Henry Morris
    - Moss, Alice, Mrs. (born circa 1831), circa 1875; (1 carte-de-visite and 2 cabinet photographs) (Box 10, Folder 389)
      Active in Ashton-under-Lyne and Dukinfield, England, 1873-1905
      Also known as Mrs. Elijah Moss or Mrs. Robert Daines
      Family portrait of Alice Webb Mellin (1841-1913) and her four children: Jonathan (1862-1933), Thomas (1863-1915), Anna (born 1864), and James (1866-1936), circa 1869
    - Müller, Marie, 1899; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 390)
      Active in Breslau (Wrocław) and Silesia (Dolnośląskie), Germany (Poland), circa 1895-1900
    - Myszkowska, A., Madame, circa 1865; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 10, Folder 391)
      Active in Paris, France, circa 1860-1870
      Portrait of a sleeping dog
    - Napoleon, Anaïs, Señora (1831-1912), circa 1860-1870; (4 cartes-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 392)
      Active in Barcelona, Spain, 1853-1912
      Also known as Señorita Anne Tiffon Cassan, Señora Fernando Napoleon, or Señora Antonio Fernández Soriano
    - Neely, Mary Myrtle Bilyeu, Mrs. (1870-1942), circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 11, Folder 393)
      Active in Mulberry Grove, Illinois, circa 1900
      Also known as Mrs. Marion Montgomery Neely
      Portrait of Eddie Brouse
    - Nellis, Louisa Jane Fish, Mrs. (1840-1910), 1866-1869; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 394)
      Active in Dayton, Ohio, 1866-1869
      Also known as Mrs. L. J. Nellis or Mrs. George Klock Nellis
    - Nelson, A. A., Mrs., 1893; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 11, Folder 395)
      Active in Woodland, California, 1893
    - Nelson, Cecilia, circa 1890-1900; (11 cartes-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 396)
      Active in Malmö, Sweden, circa 1890-1900
    - Newmon, S. J., Mrs., circa 1870-1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 397)
      Active in Pleasant Grove, Minnesota, circa 1870-1880
    - Nichols, C. A., Mrs. (born circa 1828), circa 1860-1866; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 398)
      Active in Angelica and Rochester, New York, circa 1860-1866
    - Nielsen, Sophie, circa 1895; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 399)
      Active in Aalborg, Denmark, circa 1895
    - Nikodem, Annie M., Miss, circa 1888; (7 cabinet photographs) (Box 11, Folder 400)
      Active in Chicago, Illinois, 1885-1895
      Includes a portrait of Florence M. Searles (born 1880) and a portrait of Ursula G. Marshall (born 1884) dressed as Martha Washington, circa 1890
    - Nilson, Emma, circa 1910; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 401)
      Active in Grebbestad, Sweden, circa 1910
    - Nilson, Klara, circa 1895; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 402)
      Active in Malmö, Sweden, circa 1895
    - O'Donnell, Misses, circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 11, Folder 403)
      Partnership between sisters Anna O'Donnell (born 1866, later Mrs. Alexander Rodgers) and Margaret O'Donnell, (born 1873)
      Active in Beloit, Kansas, circa 1900-1910
    - Ogle, Mary Jane Drum, Mrs. (1837-1916), circa 1860-1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 404)
      Active in Cerro Gordo, Illinois, circa 1860-1870
      Also known as Mrs. William Ogle, Drum & Ogle, or City Gallery
    - Oleson, Anna G., Mrs. (born circa 1855), 1881-1889; (7 cartes-de-visite and 1 cabinet photograph) (Box 11, Folder 405)
      Active in Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1881-1889
      Also known as Mrs. John H. Oleson, Mrs. Andrew Heighstedt, or Oleson Gallery
    - Ollson, Anna, circa 1895; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 406)
      Active in Karlstad, Sweden, 1874-1901
    - Olsen, Julie, circa 1890; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 407)
      Active in Helsingør, Denmark, circa 1890
    - Olson, Emelia, Mrs., circa 1870-1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 408)
      Active in the United States of America, circa 1870-1880
    - Osborne, Clara, Miss (born circa 1871), circa 1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 11, Folder 409)
      Active in Birmingham and Bridgnorth, England, circa 1891-1901
      Portrait of a boy ballet dancer
    - O'Shaughnessy, Miss, circa 1864; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 410)
      Active in Melbourne, Australia, circa 1862-1870
      Also known as Johnstone, O'Shannessy (sic), & Co.
    - Österlind, Ida, circa 1900-1905; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 411)
      Active in Trelleborg, Sweden, circa 1900-1905
      Portraits of a bride and groom
    - Otis, Clark, Mrs., circa 1863-1865; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 412)
      Active in Dundee, New York, circa 1863-1865
    - Overend, Mary Robinson, Mrs. (born circa 1815), circa 1865; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 413)
      Active in Hull, England, 1859-1867
      Also known as Mrs. William Overend
    - Packer, Edna, Miss (1838-1913), circa 1860-1869; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 414)
      Active in Alliance, Ohio, circa 1860-1869
    - Palmer, Sarah, Mrs. (born circa 1834), circa 1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 415)
      Active in Tomah, Wisconsin, circa 1870
      Also known as Mrs. E. N. Palmer or Mrs. Edwin N. Palmer
    - Palmkvist, Maria, circa 1910; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 416)
      Active in Skövde, Sweden, circa 1910